Hello friends, by the time you are watching this video
, the allotment has come and we have also
just checked on the live stream.  It was a very
good allotment.  Whoever applied for even one lot
definitely got one lot.  There were
very few people who were disappointed.
We were checking live pay and at least
seven to eight out of 10 applications were
getting allotment.  You guys please tell me
how it was, how many applications you made and
how much allotment you got.  Well, now that the matter of
allotment is over.  The one who was supposed to get it, got it, the one who was not supposed to get it, did
not get it, now what is it, now the
listing day is on 19th, that means tomorrow is going to be the
listing day,
what plan, what strategy should we have ready on that day, we are going to
see that thing in this video,
so our checklist will be ready,
before that we will have to prepare some points and
see as to which points
we have to take the decision.  Should we
go for the long term or for listing gains
or do
we have to make some profit in the short term and exit.
We are going to create all these views in this video.
Watch the video till the end.  If you are
new to the channel, please subscribe and
like the video.  Let's move ahead in the video.
So there is a data from ICI AMC
IPO has an EPS of 65 and is
bringing its IPO at valuations of 33 and
return on net worth is around 82%.  Ok
?  And they had shown their revenue of Rs 4900 crore
last year.
Why is it necessary to compare all these things?  If
its EPS is shown at the top, HDFC
's EPS is around 57 and that of our ICIC
AMC IPO is 65.  If you look at the PE there, the
valuation at which it is being brought
is 33 and if you look at its top, it is 45 and
41.  We will keep this in mind.
So, there was a very good demand in this IPO
and it was subscribed around 39 times in
total, out of which 123 times was
your QI and accordingly, there was a
good allotment in the retail category also.  The
PE valuation that the company
is bringing is around 33
and the company has kept its issue price at
around Rs 2165 per share.
Ok?  The GMP running
in the grey market is 17%.  If you add this, the
rate comes out to be Rs 370, if you
add this then the chances of getting listed are Rs
2535.  Ok?  If this listing
happens at this place or if we calculate a range
from 2470 to 2500, the
range is 2500 25, 2525.  If
we take the average at Rs 2500 so that the listing happens around this, then
brother, for the listing gain that you have
applied for, 15% is good for you.
You can absolutely 100% exit at 15%.
Ok?  Who has learned to list gains
who is okay?  If
you see it around, you will get a chance in 15 minutes.
You can sell.  That's it for
those at the listing end.  Ok?  Now let's
talk about the short term ones.
For short term people,
as soon as it opens at the rate of Rs 2500, you can book
50% quantity here at least at Rs 2500-2520 as I am planning to do.
Second 50%
quantity I will weight for the price of 2700.
For the price of Rs 2700.  Why?
Because the valuation that the
company is bringing is currently 33.  Ok?  If it is
listed at 2500 then it will be 39.
We have shown HDFC AMC above.  His
PE is running at 45.  If you don't push it too much and
catch 42 then this price will at
least reach you to 2700-2750.  So
when we go around this price,
this is our plan for one to three weeks.
If the price goes around this then we will
withdraw some quantity here.  Our
capital will also be freed and we will
also make good profits.
Ok?  Those who plan for the long term.
For long term investors, see the
company is already above Rs 1 lakh market cap.  Ok
?  If we get it after 3 months or 4 months, then
we can get it again at some price discount.  For
now,
I would not say to stay long term
but if you stay then
keep long term only till your
profit is safe or if it comes down deep then
you will have to add some quantity in the deep
because you should take advantage of that deep.
If you keep advertising yourself in the long term then it is
fine.  Here's your
listing and here's your plan for the short term.
How to proceed and what rate
you can get to see and
long term plan that if it hits deep below then
you should add quantity.   Only then will
you be able to reap more benefits in the long term.
So, we prepared a plan.
Ok?  The video ended here.
We are ready with a plan.  If you are
new to the channel, please subscribe.
Like the video and join the Telegram channel.  On the
day of listing,
we will come live at 9:00 am
and watch the listing together
because I have also got the allotment, so it is going to be even more
fun.